CTRL+C: Copy selected text to clipboard (copy/paste buffer)
CTRL+V: Paste from buffer
CTRL+X: Cut selected text to buffer (selected text is deleted)
CTRL+S: Save current file in VSCode
SHIFT+ALT+A: Toggle block comment in VSCode
CTRL+/: Toggle line comment in VSCode
CTRL+Right Arrow Key: Move cursor from word to word right
CTRL+Left Arrow Key: Move cursor from word to word left
CTRL+SHIFT+Right Arrow Key:Select word right
CTRL+SHIFT+Left Arrow Key:Select word left
CTRL+A: Select all contents
CTRL+L: Select current line, including end of line character
Home Key: Jump to start of line
End Key: Jump to end of line
CTRL+Home Key: Jump to beginning of current file


